ILGWU. Charles Zimmerman Collection of Radical Pamphlets 5780/178
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Wang Ming. The revolutionary movement in the colonial countries, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  Speech, revised and augmented, delivered August 7, 1935
- Robert Minor. The heritage of the Communist Political Association, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 84)
- Minutes of the National Committee of Labor's League for Political Education, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  23 September, 1950
- Finn Moe. Does Norwegian labor seek the middle way?, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 86)
- Vyacheslav Molotov. The international situation and the Soviet Union, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 87)
- Vyacheslav Molotov. The meaning of the Soviet-German non-aggression pact, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 88)
- Joseph Moody. Why are Jews persecuted?, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 89)
- Walter P. Reuther; Harry Wellington Laidler. Needed: a moral awakening in America, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  Symposium by Walter P. Reuther and others. Harry W. Laidler, editor.
- New Leader. Morals in politics: a collection of essays, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Joseph V. Moreschl. Democracy in practice: being a brief summary of the history and activities of the International Hod Carriers, Building and Common Laborers' Union of America (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Dwight C. Morgan. The foreign born in the United States, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Kenneth Morgan. Juvenile delinquency again!, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Herbert Morrison. A labor party versus fascism: exposing the bankruptcy of fascism, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Elizabeth Morrissy. What laws must we have?, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Felix Morrow. The civil war in Spain, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Philip Murray. The CIO defense plan, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Philip Murray; Abraham Joel Tobias; Maria Anastos. C.I.O. re-employment plan, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  The 1944 Murray re-employment plan defines the deflationary gap, examines the dangers therein to the nation's security and to democracy, and sets forth seven points enunciating how the deflationary gap can be filled and its dangers obviated, by Philip Mur
- Philip Murray. Technological unemployment; "the social and economic consequences of technology", 1940 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  A handbook on the effects of technological changes, and what to do about them
- Philip Murray. United for victory against disruption against disunity, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Philip Murray. Wages and war profits, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Augustus P. Gardner; Morris Hillquit; Charles P. Fagnani; M. M. Bartholomew. Must we arm?, 1916 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  A debate on the question: Resolved, that the security of the nation requires an increase of the military force of the United States; held in Carnegie Hall, New York, April 2, l915 under the auspices of the Rand School of Social Science. For the affirmat
- Abraham John Muste. The automobile industry and organized labor, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Siegfried Nacht. Answer please! Questions for communists., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  3rd revised and enlarged edition
- National Guilds League, London. National guilds: an appeal to trade unionists (Box 8, Folder 16)
- National Youth Anti-War Congress. Proceedings of the National Youth Anti-War Congress, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Edgar Ansel Mowrer. Nazi justice: Nazi law for Poles and Jews, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  Preface by Edgar Ansel Mowrer
- Scott Nearing. Another world war, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Scott Nearing. British labor bids for power The historic Scarboro Conference of the Trades Union Congress, 1926 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Scott Nearing. The decisive year, 1931: capitalism, imperialism, sovietism before the bar of history, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Scott Nearing. The law of social revolution: a co-operative study, 1926 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Scott Nearing. A Nation Divided: Or Plutocracy Versus Democracy., 1920 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Scott Nearing. Russia turns east; the triumph of soviet diplomacy in Asia, 1926 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Scott Nearing. Stopping a war: the fight of the French workers against the Moroccan campaign of 1925 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Scott Nearing. A warless world, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Scott Nearing. World labor unity, 1926 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Juan Negrin. Christianity and Spain, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Juan Negrin. Speech by Dr. Negrin, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  President of the Council of Ministers. (Barcelona, 14th October 1938)
- Franz L. Neumann; Carl Raushenbush; Harold J. Laski. European trade unionism and politics, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  Edited by Carl Raushenbush with a preface by Harold J. Laski.
- Ruth Fischer; Adolph Weingarten. The Network: Information Bulletin about Stalinist Organizations and Organizational Forms., 1944 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  no.3 (1944:March)
- The New Soviet Constitution, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- New world a'coming; a study guide on human rights., 1968 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  Prepared by a joint working party appointed by Church Women United and the National Council of Catholic Women.
- They sow distrust: commission exposes "front" organizations as enemies of public education in America, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Osgood Nichols; Comstock Glaser. Work camps for America: the German experience and the American opportunity., 1933 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Reinhold Niebuhr. Jews after the war (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Andres Nin. La huelga general de enero y sus ensenanzas (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Andres Nin; Earl R. Browder. Struggle of the trade unions against fascism, 1923 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  Introduction by Earl R. Browder
- International Labor Defense. N.L.R.B. and free speech, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Max Nomad. The Jewish conspiracy, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Joseph North. Washington and Lincoln: The American tradition, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Paul Novik. Palestine: the communist position, the colonial question, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- John A. O'Brien. The Church and a living wage, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Frank O'Hara. Credit unions, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Labour Party (Great Britain). The old world and the new society; a report on the problems of war and peace reconstruction., 1942 (Box 8, Folder 45)
- M. J. Olgin. Capitalism Defends Itself Through th Socialist Labor Party, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 46)
- M. J. Olgin. Life and teachings of Friedrich Engels, 1935 (Box 8, Folder 47)
- M. J. Olgin. That Man Browder: Communist Candidate for President., 1936 (Box 8, Folder 48)
- M. J. Olgin. Why Communism? Plain Talks on Vital Problems., 1935 (Box 8, Folder 49)
- Erich Ollenhauer. Our common concerns: a Social Democrat speaks to Americans, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 50)
- On guard against war and fascism, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  v.1:no.1 (1937:Dec.). Yiddish and English.
- Freeland League. On new soil, under new skies, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 52)
- Communist International. On the Road to Bolshevization, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 53)
- Henry A. Wallace. An Open Letter to Premier Stalin (Box 8, Folder 54)
- Blanch Freedman. Opposing the so-called Equal rights amendment (Box 8, Folder 55)
- Bernard Seaman. Order! How to Conduct a Union Meeting on Ship and Shore (Box 8, Folder 56)
  Illustrated by Bernard Seaman
- William Green. Organized labor: the home of workers of all faiths, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 57)
- Communist Party of the U.S.A. Our immediate work: program adopted by the Central Executive Committee of the Workers Party of America. (Box 8, Folder 58)
- Our present political picture, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 59)
- Thomas Ashcroft; George Hicks. An Outline of Modern Imperialism, 1922 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  Foreword by George Hicks
- Shimshon Oxman. The government of Israel, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 61)
- George Padmore. The life and struggles of Negro toilers, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 62)
- Jacob Panken. A judge sees Germany in its color (Box 8, Folder 63)
- Pen and Hammer. Don't take it lying down, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 64)
- Communist Party of the U.S.A. A people's constitution for New York, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 65)
- The people take the lead: a record of progress in civil rights, 1947 to 1951. (Box 8, Folder 66)
- John Pepper. Why every miner should be a Communist, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 67)
- Institute of International Labor Research. Los frentes populares comunistas, 1917-1956. Cuatro decades de perfidia., 1957 (Box 8, Folder 68)
- Jonathan Ellsworth Perkins; Meade McClanahan. The biggest hypocrite in America: Gerald L. K. Smith unmasked, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  Introduction by Meade McClanahan.
- Florence Peterson. Strikes in the United States, 1880-1936, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 70)
- O. Piatnitsky. The Communist parties in the fight for the masses, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 71)
- O. Piatnitsky. The immediate tasks of the international trade union movement, 1930 (Box 8, Folder 72)
- O. Piatnitsky. The work of the communist parties of France and Germany: and the tasks of the communists in the trade union movement (Box 8, Folder 73)
- Inter-American Regional Organization-ICTFU. Peron unmasked; the martyrdom of the free trade union movement in Argentina. (Box 8, Folder 74)
- Joseph S. Clark; Richardson Dilworth; Lawrence M. C. Smith. The Philadelphia story (Box 8, Folder 75)
- Morgan Phillips. Morgan Phillips tells you about the Labour Party: the party with a future., 1945 (Box 8, Folder 76)
- O. Piatnitsky. World Communists in action: the consolidation of the Communist parties and why the growing political influence of the sections of the Comintern is not sufficiently maintained, 1930 (Box 8, Folder 77)
- O. Piatnitsky. The twenty-one conditions of admission into the Communist International, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 78)
- O. Piatnitsky. The work of the communist parties of France and Germany: and the tasks of the communists in the trade union movement (Box 8, Folder 79)
- Wilhelm Pieck. Freedom, peace and bread! The activities of the Executive committee of the Communist International, 1935 (Box 8, Folder 80)
- Wilhelm Pieck. We are fighting for a Soviet Germany, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 81)
- Robert M. Pierce. The Roosevelt road to ruin, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 82)
- John Pierson. Employment after the war, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 83)
- Pioneers of labor. (Box 8, Folder 84)
- Pioneers of labor: the shoemakers, Andrew Jackson, William H. Sylvis, Terence V. Powderly, Samuel Gompers, eight-hour day, Eugene V. Debs, John Mitchell, William D. Haywood., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 85)
- Communist Party of the U.S.A. The platform of the class struggle; national platform of the Workers (communist) party, 1928. (Box 8, Folder 86)
- Communist Party of the U.S.A. Platform of struggle for urgent needs of toilers: election platform of the Communist Party, New York State, 1934. (Box 8, Folder 87)
- The Plebs, 1923 (Box 8, Folder 88)
  v.15:no.6-8 (1923:June-Aug.)
- A policy for real wages., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 89)
  A statement of policy on prices, wages and exports, approved by a conference of trade union executive committees.
- Katherin Pollak. Can the work-week shrink and wages grow? Present problems in the light of the past, 1935 (Box 8, Folder 90)
- Population problems, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 91)
- The post office ban on "Revolutionary age", 1931 (Box 8, Folder 92)
- National Community Relations Advisory Council.. Postwar employment discrimination against Jews, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 93)
- Hortense Powdermaker; Helen Frances Storen. Probing Our Prejudices, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 94)
- Preserve the Olympic ideal: a statement of the case against American participation in the Olympic games at Berlin., 1935 (Box 8, Folder 95)
- U.S. Department of Labor. The price of industrial home work and why it should be regulated., 1936 (Box 8, Folder 96)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor). Principles established by the National Labor Relations Board., 1934 (Box 8, Folder 97)
- The Problem of Tunisia., 1948-1951 (Box 8, Folder 98)
- Labour Party (Great Britain). Problems of foreign policy., 1952 (Box 8, Folder 99)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations). Producing for Victory: a labor manual for increasing war production / Prepared and compiled by International Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians-CIO., 1942 (Box 8, Folder 100)
- Steel Workers Organizing Committee. Production problems: a handbook for committeemen of local lodges of S.W.O.C., 1938 (Box 8, Folder 101)
- Union for Democratic Action. A program for Americans., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 102)
- The program of the C.I.O.: an account of major policies and decisions adopted at the conference of the Committee for Industrial Organization, Atlantic City, N.J., October, 1937. (Box 8, Folder 103)
- Communist International. Program of the Communist International, together with its constitution, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 104)
- Communist Party of the U.S.A. Program and constitution, Workers Party of America, 1922 (Box 8, Folder 105)
  Adopted at national convention, New York City, December 24, 25, 26, 1921.
- Local 22. Program of the Dressmakers Progressive Group., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 106)
- Harry Wellington Laidler; Stuart Chase. A program for labor and progressives, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 107)
  Symposium, ed. by Harry W. Laidler. Participants: Stuart Chase [and others]
- A Public statement on communism and Jews, 1935 (Box 8, Folder 108)
- The purpose of communist education (Box 8, Folder 109)
- Collective Agreement: Associated Fur Coat and Trimming Manufacturers, Inc. with the Furriers' Joint Council of New York, 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 110)
- International Red Aid. Questions and answers on fair labor standards law (Wages and Hours Act)., 1938 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Questions and answers on Palestine, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Mike Quin. The Yanks are not coming (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Karl Radek; Patrick Lavin. Proletarian dictatorship and terrorism, 1921 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  Translated by P. Lavin
- Radical review, 1918 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  v.1:no.3 (1918:Jan.); v.2:no.1-2 (1918:July-Oct/Dec.)
- Clarence Randall. America at the crossroads, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  Clarence B. Randall, President, Inland Steel Company, Chicago, Ill; opening statement on August 11, 1949, before the President's Steel Industry Board, in hearings on union demands
- Committee of 100. Rape, Justice and Florida's reputation (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Carl Raushenbush. Fordism, Ford and the workers, Ford and the community, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor). Reconstruction administration; report of the A.F. of L. Committee on post-war planning., 1944 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Herman F. Reissig. Adolph Hitler and Francisco Franco: two minds with but a single thought, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Religion faces war and fascism (Box 9, Folder 11)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations). Report of the CIO delegates to the World trade union conference, London, February 1945. (Box 9, Folder 12)
- SUNY. Committee on Medical Education Centers. Report of the Committee on medical education centers, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- RILU (Red International of Labor Unions). Report of the fourth congress of the R.I.L.U., 1928 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- International Clothing Workers' Federation. Report of the Fourth International Clothing Workers' Congress, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  June 15th-17th, 1930 in Leipsic.
- Iosif Reznikov. Trade union organisation in U. S. S. R., 1927 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Young Communist League. Resolution on the immediate tasks in the fight for the working youth (Box 9, Folder 17)
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America). Resolutions adopted at the 17th biennial convention of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America., 1950 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Communist Party of the U.S.A. Resolutions of the ninth convention of the Communist Party of the U.S.A., 1936 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Georgi Dimitroff. Resolutions; including also the closing speech of Georgi Dimitroff., 1935 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Resolutions of the conference-congress [of the] World Federation of Trade Unions, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  September 25 to October 8, 1945
- Resolutions and Dicisions of the Red Labor Union International., 1921 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Resolutions and Dicisions Second World Congress of the Red Labor Union International., 1922 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Walter P. Reuther. Peace, plenty, politics, and people, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  Testimony of Walter P. Reuther before the Platform Committee of the National Democratic Convention, Chicago, July 21, 1952.
- Railroad Brotherhoods Unity Movement. Revolt in the railroad unions, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Communist International. The revolutionary movement in the colonies, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  Thesis adopted by the sixth World Congress of the Communist International.
- Revolutionary socialist review; a quarterly devoted to Marxian socialism., 1934-1935 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  v. 1, no. 1-4; Nov. 1934-autumn 1935.
- J. C. Rich. Labor's national hero, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  Samuel Gompers Centennial Committee
- AFL (American Federation of Labor). The rights of labor: democracy vs. totalitarianism., 1947 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- A. W. Ricker. The political economy of Jesus, 1912 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- George Ridley. India, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Roger Baldwin; Zechariah Chafee; Melvyn Douglas; William Green; Philip Murray; A. Philip Randolph; Joseph Schlossberg; Paul Murray; Murray Kempton; Frank P. Graham. The rights of man are worth defending, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  Articles by Roger Baldwin, Zechariah Chafee, Melvyn Douglas, William Green, Philip Murray, A. Philip Randolph, and Joseph Schlossberg. "All for Mr. Davis": Odell Waller's story told by Paul Murray and Murray Kempton...with a preface by President Frank P.
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations). The Right to Strike: Keystone of Liberty, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Labour Party (Great Britain). The rise of the Labour Party., 1946 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Anna Rochester. Wall street, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Harry Wellington Laidler. The role of the races in our future civilization, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Bill: an act respecting industrial standards., 1935 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Serafino Roumaldi. Labor and Democracy in Latin America, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  Reprinted from Foreign Affairs.
- Serafino Roumaldi. A Look at the Latin American Labor Scene (Box 9, Folder 39)
  Reprinted from The Pan American
- Waverley Lewis Root. Are you ready for world war III?, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Lawrence K. Rosinger. Forging a new China, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Arthur Max Ross. The influence of unionism upon earnings, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Irwin Ross. The town that took its own pulse; a report on the lessons in democracy Montclair taught itself., 1950 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Rules for union meetings, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Rumor clinic. (Box 9, Folder 45)
- British Trades Union Delegation to Russia and Caucasia. Russia today, the official report of the British Trade Union delegation., 1925 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Charles E. Ruthenberg. The Workers (Communist) Party: what it stands for, why workers should join, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- John Augustine Ryan. The Constitution and Catholic industrial teaching, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Samuel Gompers. Samuel Gompers' credo: quotations from his speeches and writings., 1950 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Karl F. M. Sandberg. The Soviet Union, the land of the common man, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 50)
- Louis Schaffer. Stalin's fifth column on Broadway: a clue to theatre people, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 51)
- Harry Scherman; Herman Rauschning. What is this war about?, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  An analysis of Herman Rauschning's "The revolution of nihilism."
- Edgar Schmiedeler. Balanced abundance, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 53)
- Edgar Schmiedeler. Consumers' cooperatives, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 54)
- Edgar Schmiedeler. Our rural proletariat, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 55)
- Edgar Schmiedeler. The rural South: problem or prospect?, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 56)
- Edgar Schmiedeler. Vanishing homesteads, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 57)
- American Committee for Democracy and Intellectual Freedom. Science condemns racism: a reply to the Chamber of Commerce of the State of New York, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 58)
- Schools and fishin' poles (Box 9, Folder 59)
- Scottsboro, a record of a broken promise, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 60)
- Seafarer Sam says (Box 9, Folder 61)
- Seafarers organizing program (Box 9, Folder 62)
- Seafarers organizers handbook (Box 9, Folder 63)
- Workers Party of America. The second year of the Workers Party of America, 1924 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  Report of the Central Executive Committee to the Third Nation Convention held in Chicago, Ill., Dec. 30, 31, 1923 and Jan. 1, 2, 1924: theses, program, resolutions.
- Joel Seidman. A labor party for America?, 1936 (Box 9, Folder 65)
- Joel Seidman; Jack London; Bernard Karsh. Why workers join unions (Box 9, Folder 66)
- Gilbert Seldes. Against revolution, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 67)
- Sell union service and build union jobs (Box 9, Folder 68)
  ads for home milk delivery
- Clarence Senior. Democracy comes to a cotton kingdom; the story of Mexico's La Laguna, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 69)
- Max Shachtman. 1871: the Paris commune (Box 9, Folder 70)
- Max Shachtman; Robert Minor. Lenin, Liebknecht, Luxemburg, 1925 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  Introduction by Robert Minor.
- In the shadow of fear: American liberties 1948-49., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 72)
- Charles Sherman. Jews after the war: the test of security, a symposium on the Jewish question, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 73)
- Charles Sherman; Xavier Gonzales. Labor's enemy: anti-Semitism, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  Illustrated by Xavier Gonzales
- Max Sherover. When profits cease: a timely warning to capitalists., 1960 (Box 9, Folder 75)
- Seafarers' International Union of North America. Shipboard handbook for crewmembers and delegates (Box 9, Folder 76)
- Should labor support Roosevelt (Box 9, Folder 77)
- David Shub; Robert J. Alexander; Norman Angell. What do you know about British labor? (Box 9, Folder 78)
  Introduction by Norman Angell
- A. M. Simons. Class struggles in America, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  2nd edition, revised and enlarged
- Upton Sinclair. The flivver king, a story of Ford-America, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 80)
- Upton Sinclair. No pasaran! (They shall not pass) A story of the battle of Madrid., 1937 (Box 9, Folder 81)
- Resume of the proceedings of the sixteenth National Conference on Labor Legislation, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  Novemeber 29, 30, and December 1, 1949.
- Richard Dana Skinner. Debt system or property system?, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 83)
- Walter Citrine. Slavery under Hitler's "new order,", 1941 (Box 9, Folder 84)
  Foreword by Walter Citrine.
- Preston Slosson; Grayson Kirk. Swords of Peace, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 85)
- Sasha Small. Ten years of labor defense, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 86)
- H. G. Smeland. World Peace: Reconstruction and readjustment, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 87)
- Gerald L. K. Smith. Is Communism Jewish? (Box 9, Folder 88)
- Gerald L. K. Smith. The crime of crimes: a statement to the U.S. Senate Judiciary Committee, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 89)
- Vern Smith. The Frame-up System., 1930 (Box 9, Folder 90)
- TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America). So you're a steward! A handbook for TWUA shop stewards and department committees, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  3rd edition
- Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands (Social Democratic Party of Germany). The Social Democratic Party of Germany., 1953 (Box 9, Folder 92)
- Socialist Party (U.S.). A militant program for the Socialist Party of America, 1918-1933 (Box 9, Folder 93)
- Roy E. Burt. Socialist handbook: 1937 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  Introduction by Roy E. Burt, executive secretary.
- Socialist Ministers Conference. Proceedings, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  Evanston, Illinois, June 25- 28, 1934, held under the auspices of the Socialist Ministers' Fellowship, Midwest Section, and the Chicago Committee of Christian Socialists.
- Socialist Party: words and deeds., 1933 (Box 9, Folder 96)